<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ashton Bradley</title>
    <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ashton Bradley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021; All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:21:20 +1300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Paper published</title>
      <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:21:20 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Our work on &amp;hellip; appeared in &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Short Bio </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/code/</guid>
      <description>Code Open source for open science! More packages will come here as we develop more julia tools for computational physics.
Julia code on Github  VortexDistributions.jl PhaseSpaceTools.jl QuantumFluidSpectra.jl ScalingDynamics.jl &amp;hellip;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/media/</guid>
      <description>Media  New findings on Fluid Turbulence, Ashton Bradley on Nights with Bryan Crump, Radio New Zealand 2019 Otago–Queensland researchers observe 70-year-old prediction, with wide-reaching effects Order emerges from chaos in 2D vortices, Ashton Bradley in Physics Today 2019 Quantum Entanglement at an Individual Atom Scale, Ashton Bradley work with Mikkel Anderson&amp;rsquo;s group in DWC annual report 2018 Emergent Non-Eulerian Hydrodynamics of Quantum Vortices in Two Dimensions, Asia-Pacific Physics News Letter, p 60 Otago Research Helping to Unlock Superfluid Mysteries, Ashton Bradley in Otago Daily Times 2015 Rutherford Discovery Fellowship, Ashton Bradley in Otago Daily Times 2010 Quantum Whirlpools, Ashton Bradley and Crispin Gardiner on Our Changing World with Veronika Meduna, Radio New Zealand 2008 Vortices spontaneously arise as a Bose-Einstein condensate forms, Ashton Bradley in Physics Today 2008 Teleportation method proposed by Australian scientists, Ashton Bradley in Physics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Peer reviewed publications online arXiv preprints | Google Scholar | Publons | Scopus | orcid.org/0000-0002-3027-3195
Preprints Spin-orbit- and coherently-coupled spin-1 Bose-Einstein condensates under rotation,
Paramjeet Banger, R. Kishor Kumar, Ashton S. Bradley, Sandeep Gautam
arXiv
Emergence of off-axis equilibria in a quantum vortex gas,
Matthew T. Reeves, Kwan Goddard-Lee, Guillaume Gauthier, Oliver R. Stockdale, Hayder Salman, Timothy Edmonds, Xiaoquan Yu, Ashton S. Bradley, Mark Baker, Halina Rubinsztein-Dunlop, Matthew J. Davis, Tyler W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/theses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashtonsbradley.github.io/theses/</guid>
      <description>Student Theses BSc (Hons)  Mathew Denys (Otago 2018), Triplet Down Conversion using Optical Phase Space Methods Peter Barnett (Otago 2017), Two-Time Correlations of an Energy-Damped Bose-Einstein Condensate Zaki Atayee (Otago 2016), Kohn Mode Damping in a Bose-Einstein Condensate Michael Cawte (Otago 2016), Vortex Dynamics and Spectra Fluctuations in a Superfluid Disk Rob McDonald (Otago 2013), Decay of Persistent Current in a Two-Dimensional Superfluid Malcolm Morrison (Otago 2013), A Quantum Kuramoto Model Kyle Wright (Otago 2010), Decay of a dark soliton in a warm Bose-Einstein condensate: a variational approach Samuel Rooney (Otago 2009), Single Vortex Dynamics in High Temperature Bose-Einstein Condensates  MSc  Eric Xu (Otago 2021) Jordan Clark (Otago 2021) Michael Cawte (Otago 2019), Snell’s Law and Necklace States for Vortex Dipoles in a Quantum Gas Rob McDonald (Otago 2015), C-Field Theory of Dynamics in One Dimensional Bose Gases: The Kibble-Zurek Mechanism and Bright Soliton Arrest Matthew Reeves (Otago 2013), Inverse Energy Cascade in Two-Dimensional Quantum Turbulence Samuel Rooney (Otago 2011), C-field description of the quasi-equilibrium Bose gas: persistent currents and Kelvon-induced vortex decay  PhD  Rob McDonald (Otago 2019), Anomalous Dissipation in Bose Gases: Analytic Theory of Energy Damping Matthew Reeves (Otago 2017), Quantum Analogues of Two-Dimensional Classical Turbulence Sam Rooney (Otago 2014), Implementation and Applications of the Stochastic Projected Gross-Pitaevskii Equation [Science Division Exceptional Thesis Award]  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
